I heard that the new beauty commercial director
听说新来的美女商务总监
And Xu were always childhood sweethearts
和徐总是青梅竹马
Isn't it a perfect match
也太配了吧
This is a perfect match
这门当户对
The degree of childhood sweetheart
青梅竹马的程度
I dare not even write novels like this
连小说都不敢这么写呀
That's a good match, isn't it?
好配啊 太配了吧
It matches a face too well
配一脸 太配了
Lulu, have you seen the new beauty
露露新来的美女看见了吗
They match well, they match well
他们好配啊好配
I'm getting high. I'm getting high
嗑到了嗑到了
Pair-to-pair match-to-match
对对对 配配配
What bah bah ah
什么 呸呸呸啊
Why didn't you go with your childhood sweetheart
呦怎么没去陪你的青梅竹马呀
Be jealous
吃醋了
No
才没有
I said it was going public
我都说要公开了
You have to say this and that yourself
是你自己非要说这说那的
Then I'll go
那我走
Hey
哎
Feng, let's have dinner together tonight
阿枫晚上我们一起吃个饭吧
Good
好
Sorry to be late
不好意思来晚了
Let me introduce Xu Nanfeng, a handsome boy
我介绍一下大帅哥徐楠枫
This is our birthday girl today, Jia Jia
这个是我们今天的寿星佳佳
Happy birthday
生日快乐
Thank you for the cake, handsome boy
谢谢大帅哥送的蛋糕
Now that everyone is here, let's drink one
既然人齐了那我们喝一个吧
Come and wish Jiajia a happy birthday
来祝佳佳生日快乐
Happy birthday
生日快乐
Thank you
谢谢
Sit down. Sit down. Don't be too restrained
坐吧坐吧不要太拘束了
Feng, do you remember adults when we were young
阿枫你还记得大人在我们小时候
Got us a young marriage
给我们定了娃娃亲
I was dark and fat at that time
那时候我又黑又胖
You are thin in vain
你白白瘦瘦
People thought you were our child bride
人家还以为你是我们家的童养媳
Don't know
不知道
My mother also said that I haven't seen my aunt for a long time
我妈妈还说很久没见阿姨了
Visit your aunt at home another day
改天去家里拜访阿姨
Grandma was very kind to me when I was a child
奶奶在我小时候对我特别好
I miss Grandma too
我也好想奶奶啊
Don't you mind my grandma is good to everyone
你也别在意我奶奶对谁都好
Don't be so polite in private
私底下就别这么客气
Just call me Ball Ball
叫我球球就好
My girlfriend will be unhappy
我女朋友会不开心
I don't want her to be unhappy
我不希望她不开心
It's impossible for you with your little girlfriend
就你那小女朋友你们根本不可能啊
You don't know your family as well as I do, do you
你不会还没有我了解你们家吧
Let me ask you, do you dare to take her home
我问你 你敢带她回家吗
Don't you know what's going on in your home now
你家现在什么情况你心里没数吗
My family can really help you
我家才真正能帮到你的
Let's play a game
我们来玩游戏吧
Old rule, truth or adventure, men first
老规矩真心话大冒险 男士优先
But these
可是这些
What does it have to do with yourself
跟你本人有什么关系
You have a good brain
你脑子很好
Can stand alone in the company
在公司能独挡一面
People are very kind
人很善良
These are the points that have something to do with yourself
这些啊才是跟你本身有关系的点
It's not me you like either
你喜欢的也不是我
It's just that your family makes you feel
只是你家里让你觉得
You should like me
你就应该会喜欢我
Because I'm the right person
因为我门当户对
Childhood sweetheart
青梅竹马
But you don't even know me
可是你甚至都不了解我
Maybe Yulu and I don't have the so-called matching conditions
或许玉露和我并没有所谓匹配的条件
But we love each other and the three views are consistent
但我们彼此相爱三观相合
These are in my eyes
这些在我眼里
It's far more important than what you said
要远比你说的那些重要多
The designer of this project is you
这个项目的设计师是您
It's me
是我
This is my first big order in the company
这可是我来公司的第一个大单
A list of 2 million
200万的单子
Don't hold me back
你可不要给我拖后腿
I didn't expect our director Chen to have such a good figure
没想到咱们陈总监身材这么有料
If I had known, I would have met somewhere else
早知道就约在别的地方见面了
Mr. Lu is polite
陆总客气
You can come to our restaurant for a drink when you are free
有空来我们家餐厅可以过来喝喝酒
It's covered
盖好了
Please apologize to our director
请您跟我们总监道歉
Apologize for what apology
道歉道什么歉
Oh, not really
哎 不至于吧
The offender is not qualified to say so much
侵犯人的一方没有资格说至不至于吧
I was just kidding
我就是开个玩笑
We can't afford to joke so much, can we
咱们没有这么开不起玩笑的吧
Right, Director Chen
是吧陈总监
I just happened to see your screensaver
我刚刚无意间看到了您的屏保
You have a daughter, too
您也有女儿吧
Do you think this sentence can be said to your daughter
您觉得这句话能对您女儿说吗
What you can't say to your daughter
不能对自己女儿说的话
Why would you tell someone else's daughter
为什么要对别人的女儿说
Okay, two million, two million
好了200万200万
If you still want to save a little face,
如果您还想保留一点面子
Then this matter will be settled
那么就把这件事情解决了
Or I'll have to think about it
否则我就要好好想一想
How to communicate with your lover
怎么跟你爱人沟通一下
Why do you want to help me
为什么要帮我呀
Shouldn't you bother me
不应该烦我吗
Bother you, but that's between us
烦你 但那是我俩之间的事
He's right
他说的没错
You really deserve it
你确实值得
I should say goodbye to my first love
我应该跟我的初恋说再见了
Let's go
走吧
Woman
女人
Don't understand
搞不懂
Grandma, why are you here
奶奶 你怎么过来了
Hey
哎
Miss Chiang
蒋小姐
Why are you here, too
你怎么也在这里啊